ultimategamecard.com 2010-12-22

# Privacy Statement | Ultimate Game Card

[Last updated on March 31, 2010]

This privacy statement covers the domain **ULTIMATEGAMECARD.COM**. This statement demonstrates our commitment to our users' privacy. This statement covers the following topics, generally considered the most sensitive to users concerned about their privacy:

  1. What personally identifiable information PlaySpan Inc. collects. 
  2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site. 
  3. What organization collects the information. 
  4. How PlaySpan Inc. uses the information. 
  5. With whom PlaySpan Inc. may share user information. 
  6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 
  7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under PlaySpan Inc. control.
  8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

PlaySpan Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact PlaySpan Inc. at [support@playspan.com](mailto:support@playspan.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at [http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

**Information Collection**  
We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password

**Information Use**  
We use this information to

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Provide the financial services you requested
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts

**Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [support@playspan.com](mailto:support@playspan.com). We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

**_PlaySpan Inc. complies with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union._**

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. UltimateGameCard.com may set session cookies on your computer. These session cookies only hold data while you are actively using our site and expire once you leave our web site or when you close your browser. We may also set a persistent cookie on your computer to track customer flow across our site. We do not tie Personally Identifiable Information (PII) to cookies.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by UltimateGameCard.com only and does not cover the use of cookies on sites operated by any of the sites that may have links on UltimateGameCard.com.

******Profile**  
We do not store information collected through third parties to create a profile of our users. A "profile" is stored information kept on individual users that details their viewing preferences. PlaySpan Inc. uses log files only to track web site usage. These log files do not contain information that is tied to unique users or their use of our site.

******Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp,and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a service-related announcement. For instance, if there is an issue regarding the use of our Web sites we might send users an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Third Party Advertisers**  
PlaySpan Inc. does not share Web site usage information about users with any third party for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site and other sites.

**Service Providers**  
We partner with other third parties to provide specific services (For example, with "PayByCash" for payment processing) When the user signs up for one of these particular services, we may share names, or other contact information like an email address that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties' use of that personally identifiable information is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event PlaySpan Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email and prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If, as a result of the business transition, the users’ personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [support@playspan.com](mailto:support@playspan.com).

We enable you to create a profile, and share information such as messages, photos, and videos with others. Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, PlaySpan Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Security**  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information..

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees or contractors who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our account management service representatives are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees or contractors must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk unattended. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. At the time of hire and every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a locked facility. 

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can email us at [support@playspan.com.](mailto:support@playspan.com)

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  
If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please email us at [support@playspan.com.](mailto:support@playspan.com)
